ANDRÉ LISBOA

andrelisboa.co



PROFILE

Hi, my name is André Lisboa and I've been working as a UI/UX designer since 2015. Throughout my professional journey, I've worked in several companies focusing on digital products. I provide all the necessary demands of a UI designer, with emphasis on design systems, handoff for development, structuring of interfaces, as well as visual design.

In addition, I have been working as a UI/UX teacher on the Alura platform since 2018. I have launched 19 courses and over 15,000 students have accessed them in the last 6 months

CONTACT

al.andrelisboa90@gmail.com

+55 (21) 99385-3311

São Paulo - SP

SKILLS

UI/UX Design; Design Systems; Visual design; Responsive design; User testing; Handoff for devs

EDUCATION



Visual Design

PUC-Rio 2011-2015

LANGUAGES



Portuguese

Native



English

Fluent





Can communicate



Learning

EXPERIENCE



UI/UX Teacher

Alura Online Courses

Since 2018

Since 2018, I have been teaching UI design at the Alura course school. I have launched 19 courses with themes that explore the world of UI and UX.

UI Designer

Fluency Academy

2022-2023

Between 2022 and 2023, I worked at Fluency as a Senior UI Designer. My goal was to evolve the brand's products with UI design.

UI Designer

Afinz Bank

2021-2022

My main objective with the company was the construction of the design system, along with the creation of flows and functionalities.

UI/UX Designer

Super Revendedores

2018-2020

At Super Revendedores, I was responsible for the entire creation and evolution of the platform in terms of design. I was responsible for creating new journeys and flows for the system, which existed on the website, iOS, and Android.

qx3 UI/UX Designer

QX3

2016-2018

My first experience as a graduated UI designer, I was responsible for the evolution of the Sunset corporate events application.